<CreaditDetails>
  <Details Name="sc_card_name">
  <Feature>American Express Platinum Credit Card</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_cashback_percent">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_airmile_per_sgd">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_main_benefit">
  <Feature>Auto-enrolment with the Frequent Traveller Option, and a waiver of S$40 enrolment fees. Cardmember can redeem your points with over 40 of the world's renowned airlines.</Feature>
  <Feature>Complimentary The Far Card Membership worth S$425. Up to 50% savings when dining at a wide selection of restaurants islandwide. 1 for 1 drinks or complimentary bespoke cocktails/beer at most fashionable bars in Singapore.</Feature>
  <Feature>Earn 2 Membership Rewards Points for every $1.60 spent. Earn 10 Membership Rewards Points for every S$1.60 spent at Platinum EXTRA partners (eg: Reebonz, Harvery Norman, Montblanc).</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_main_benefit_rating">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_promotion_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_promotion_cond">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_promotion_end">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_gift_details">
  <Feature>2 options available: </Feature><Feature>1. Full Fee Offer: Samsung Tab A with S Pen (8.0&#8221;) with wifi worth S$551 + Tumi Vapor Luggage worth S$825</Feature><Feature>2. First Year Fee Waiver Offer: First year fee waiver worth S$321 + Samsonite Armet Spinner 57cm worth S$380</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_gift_cond">
  <Feature>1. Galaxy Tab A with S Pen (8.0"): Pay the full annual fee of $321 upfront.</Feature><Feature>2. TUMI VAPOR International Carry-on Travel Luggage and Samsonite Armet Spinner 57cm Expandable Luggage: Card members have to charge a min spend of $7500 spend within the first 6 months of the card approval to be eligible for the gift.</Feature><Feature>3. First Year Fee Waiver: Only applies to brand new American Express Card Members who do not have any other existing American Express Cards</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_gift_end">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_annual_fee">
  <Feature>321.00</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_sup_annual_fee">
  <Feature>160.50</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_fc_trans_fee">
  <Feature>2.50%</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_other_fee">
  <Feature>Fee Waiver</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_local_income">
  <Feature>50000</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_foreigner_income">
  <Feature>60000</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_main_card_age">
  <Feature>21</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_sup_card_age">
  <Feature>18</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_disclosure">
  <Feature>If your account has three or more defaults and/or one default unpaid for two or more consecutive months, 29.99% interest p.a. will be charged instead.</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_airmiles_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_airmiles_rating">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_cashback_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_cashback_rating">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_dining_details">
  <Feature>Receive a complimentary Palate Membership worth S$457.96 (inclusive of GST), which entitles you to up to 50% savings at a wide selection of popular restaurants.</Feature><Feature>Receive a complimentary The Far Card Classic Membership worth S$425 (inclusive of GST), which entitles you to special savings for unlimited visits at your choice of 11 restaurants at Fairmont Singapore, Swiss&#195;&#180;tel The Stamford Singapore, Equinox Complex and Swiss&#195;&#180;tel Merchant Court.</Feature><Feature>Get up to 50% off at over 60 of Singapore's best restaurants with American Express Selects</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_dining_rating">
  <Feature>5</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_entertainment_details">
  <Feature>Complimentary green fees and privileged access to over 40 clubs in Singapore, Philippines, Malaysia, Indonesia and Thailand</Feature><Feature>Complimentary drinks at over a dozen of Singapore's most fashionable bars including Bitters &amp; Love, Maison Ikkoku and The Mad Men Attic Bar</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_entertainment_rating">
  <Feature>5</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_grocery_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_grocery_rating">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_petrol_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_petrol_rating">    
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_rewards_details">
  <Feature>$1.60 = 2 Membership points</Feature><Feature>Get 10X Membership points at over 300 Platinum Partner outlets including G2000, Topshop and Harvey Norman</Feature><Feature>No expiry for Membership points</Feature><Feature>Redeem points from over 200 rewards in the Membership Rewards Catelogue, ranging from fine-dining, fashion to electronics</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_rewards_rating">   
  <Feature>5</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_shopping_details">
  <Feature>Get 10X Membership points at over 300 Platinum Partner outlets including G2000, Topshop and Harvey Norman</Feature><Feature>90-days return guarantee, return almost any purchase made in Singapore for a refund up to S$800 per item</Feature><Feature>Redeem vouchers with points at various shops including Dorothy Perkins, TOPSHOP, Ben Sherman, Robinsons, Isetan, OG, Courts and many more</Feature></Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_shopping_rating">
  <Feature>5</Feature></Details>

  <Details Name="sc_student_details">
  </Details>
  
  <Details Name="sc_student_rating">
  </Details>

  <Details Name="sc_main_image">
  <Feature>./images/American Express Platinum Credit Card.png</Feature></Details>

</CreaditDetails>